glassesshop.com 2019-05-01

# Privacy | Glassesshop.com

###### Privacy & Security Policies

GlassesShop.com is strongly committed to protecting your privacy and to providing a safe online experience for all our users. We take the protection of your personal data very seriously. With this privacy notice, we would like to inform you about our strict security measures and to identify what personal data is collected and discarded.

###### The Information We Collect

We collect only essential customer information such as your mailing address, phone number, email address, vision data and credit card information. The contact information you provide will only be used to contact you when necessary. All vision data and credit card information will be used for the sole purpose of billing you for the products and services that you select. We respect your privacy and we do not and will not willingly share the information you provide to us with outside companies or organizations.

###### Security Policy

Security for all Personal Information is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers. Personal Information collected by our Website is stored in secure operating environments unavailable to the public. All transactions are protected by Trustwave, a world-renowned online security system. It ensures as completely as possible that every transaction is 100% safe. With the rise in fraudulent use of credit card information over the Internet, GlassesShop.com takes credit card security very seriously. Our accounting department may at times request additional information regarding the credit card account that is being used during a purchase to ensure that no improper use takes place. We are dedicated to protecting your best interests, and we believe that you will appreciate our conviction to keep your information secure.

###### About Virtual Try-on

When using our Virtual Try-On program, you are responsible for deleting all non-proprietary photos uploaded to the user center. If you do not do this, GlassesShop.com will not be liable for any possible infringement issues that may result.

###### Choice and Opt-Out

If you do not wish to receive promotional communications from GlassesShop.com, you may "opt-out" by following the instructions included in each communication or by e-mailing the Company at [service@glassesshop.com](mailto:service@glassesshop.com).
